The Princess Sapphire
Knight of the Ribbon
Atashi no miru yume himitsu nano
The dreams I see are my secret
Dare ni mo iwanai himitsu nano
I won’t tell anyone—it’s my secret
Akai manto hira hira
A red cape fluttering
Uma o tobasu oujo
Galloping on a horse—the princess
Sore ga atashi
That’s me!
Lula dula lula dula
Lulu laa, lulaa
Ribon no kishi wa
The Knight of the Ribbon,
Honto wa hontto wa
Truly, truly,
Atashi nano sa
It’s really me!
Forty-Eighth Episode
The Bounty
Put the load on the right!
- It's me!
- I'm opening right away!
Hey, everyone!
If you want to earn a million
dollars in one night, listen to me!
A million?!
- What? Dollars?! - Do you know
the Princess of Silverland?
- The one called Sapphire?
- Yeah, exactly her!
She must be kidnapped!
I mean, bring her here alive!
So, friends, what do you say?
For what purpose kidnap her?
No questions, men!
A million dollars
to anyone who brings her here!
Tonight, the back entrance
of the castle will not be guarded,
nor locked!
Good luck!
Did you hear how much he offered!
It's still more profitable
than being a pirate.
It's so quiet..
Too quiet!
I fear this silence
is a prelude to something bad.
What's the matter, Princess?
Is that you, Doctor Uranaru?
I can't sleep,
it's too quiet.
Yes, I was thinking the same thing
It’s strange... While I was coming
here, I didn't see in the corridors...
...any soldiers on guard.
How come?
What? No guards?! And why?
Hey, guards! Guards!
Guards!
- It should work.
- Of course it will work!
You’ll see that everything will be fine!
Yeah!
That bounty, we’re definitely
the ones who are going to bag it!
You’ve got it all wrong,
brothers! That loot will be ours!
Get them!
We’ve already got that money
in our pockets! Let's move!
For this job,
you need professionals.
He’s fast asleep!
Damn, she wasn't sleeping!
I was expecting some villains like you! Who are you?
Now that you're awake, we'll have to resort to force.
- Come on!
- Be a good girl, get in the bag!
It's you, Captain Blood! What a pleasure to see you!
Hello, old friend Blood! You want the bounty all for yourself, don't you?
The bounty?!
Thanks, Blood! But what did those two want?
What are you doing?!
I brought you Princess Sapphire. Pay me the bounty.
It's really her! Well done!
Here is the bounty.
Where am I? What have you done, Captain Blood?
What is this? You know each other?
Why did you hit me earlier?
And who might this individual be?
Don't be silly and don't talk to me like that!
- It bothers me!
- Captain Blood is right!
You ask too many questions and you're too arrogant!
But Captain Blood...
Now that I've collected the bounty that was on you,
you no longer interest me! Goodbye!
Wait, Captain!
I'm coming with you!
- You aren't going anywhere!
- What?!
What do you want?
Why can't I leave?
You will stay with us for three days.
- That's why!
- Three days with you?!
Damn it!
What are these explosions?
There must be something on the bottom!
But this is a workshop!
Listen to me well! Did
you hear the explosions?
That means the tests were successful!
You will bring the gunpowder
to Silverland in several trips!
You must bring all the powder
to Silverland by tomorrow evening!
The day after tomorrow, or at noon
on the third day,
we will set off the powder
and blow up the entire city.
Rest assured that we will destroy
the entire kingdom of Silverland!
What do you say? Doesn't this
official notice seem like a good idea?
Yes, not bad...
It will place upon Sapphire...
...all the blame for the disasters
that will occur!
You're right, it will be a laugh!
It says that they will build
an amusement park for children!
All the buildings located
in this area will be destroyed.
Anyone who does not obey the order
will be sentenced to death on the spot!
The signature
is Princess Sapphire's!
Our houses! What cruelty!
It was she herself who ordered it!
She's tearing down our houses just
to make an amusement park!
Whatever has gotten into her?!
I didn't expect this
from Princess Sapphire!
Where will we live, now that
our houses are destroyed?
- Hey, Sapphire!
- Who is calling me?
I thought I heard
Blood's voice!
Ah, it's you!
What have you come here to do?
Silence!
What was that noise out there?
I want to know what happened!
Boss, I caught this man
...who was walking
in front of Sapphire's room.
- Captain Blood!
- Yes, it's me:
- Captain Blood, the pirate!
- Damn!
Hey, boss, wait a moment!
I came here...
...because I would like to change
my line of work.
You don't earn much
being a pirate.
I think you understand me
Good!
Then have Sapphire come here!
An "X"! You belong
to the X Union, as I suspected!
Why did you bring me here?
Go on, tell me what
your evil plan is!
You amuse me! I was told
that you are a spirited girl!
Tell me, though:
do you know this man or not?
Captain Blood! How did you
know that they brought me here?
I really thought
that you had sold me!
But who the hell are you?
I’ve never seen you, brat!
Haven't you realized
yet? I don’t know you!
You’re mistaking me
for someone else!
Wait!
Blood, I can’t believe
that you’ve betrayed me!
I have a feeling that something
terrible is about to happen!
Open up! Open up, quickly!
I have nothing to do with
the Princess of Silverland...
...or whoever she is!
I just want to stay with you...
...and have the money!
- I will satisfy you!
I think you can be useful to me.
You two, escort him
to the laboratory!
Haven't you learned
not to trust yet?
Hey, what nonsense is this?
Union X is not
as naive as you think.
We don't trust you,
so you will stay there all night.
Princess, you have exceeded
the limits of our patience!
- This is too much now!
- It's true, he's right!
I feel sorry for you, people!
You're right to be angry!
The Princess must be crazy
for having ordered...
...sweeping away the houses to make
room for an amusement park!
She cannot treat
her subjects like this,
who have always respected
and revered her on every occasion!
However... you must respect
this official ordinance,
otherwise you will be imprisoned
and your assets confiscated!
Oh, poor people of Silverland!
How you are being harassed!
Nylon is a good actor!
The gunpowder will arrive
in town this afternoon,
so they will blow up
what remains of Silverland.
Naturally,
it will be easy for Union X..
to conquer the kingdom of Silverland,
reduced to a pile of rubble!
Grand Duke Duralumin!
Greetings to you,
my most gracious Queen!
Is it true that Sapphire has given orders
to tear down many houses in town,
to make room
for an amusement park?
Yes, exactly so, Your Majesty!
Now the Princess, your daughter...
...is inspecting the work and
said she would not return...
- until it is finished.
- Oh, woe is us!
I cannot believe she
would do such a thing.
I would like to ask her personally.
What could have happened
to her? Sapphire, come home!
Let me out! Open up!
What do you intend to do?
You will not conquer Silverland!
Father! Mother! Forgive
me! Forgive my helplessness!
Quick, open the
underwater tunnel!
We must bring the gunpowder
to Silverland within an hour!
The prisoner is breaking free!
The man hasn't been born yet
who can put Captain Blood in a cage!
Who is that bastard throwing
dynamite into the fortress?
Sapphire! Quick!
I've come to save you!
Captain Blood!
- Thank you for coming.
- Come on, we must hurry!
Now I'll free you from your chain!
They want to destroy what
remains of the city of Silverland...
...with gunpowder!
- What?!
We must escape
quickly from this place!
Don't let that bastard escape!
Catch him and feed
him to the sharks!
A thousand dollar reward
to whoever finds Sapphire!
This way!
- There they are!
- Let's get them!
Captain Blood, you
were putting on an act...
...to discover the true intentions
of Union X, weren't you?
Of course! I did all this for
you and for your kingdom.
Now listen to me, Sapphire:
get out of here and run...
...to Silverland, to prevent
the city from being destroyed.
- And what will you do, Captain?
- Don't worry about me.
First of all, you must save
your country.
All right! Thank you, Blood!
Damn it! Is it possible that you
still haven't caught those two?!
- I'm here!
- What the hell!
Hey, you don't scare me!
I can take down all of you by
myself, henchmen of Union X!
You let Sapphire escape,
you damned imbecile!
- I won't forgive you for this!
- Come at me, come on!
What are you waiting for? Come
on, you have to take him out!
Hurry, Sapphire! I'll take
care of stopping them!
Look,
that's gunpowder!
They want to blow up the
houses with that! We'll blow up too!
We have placed
all the powder, sir.
Great! Soldier, now all
that's left is to light the fuses!
Come on, get to it!
Hey, you! Stop! Where are you going?
Let's get her! It's the Princess!
Good heavens!
It will be a disaster
if I don't hurry!
Go, Opal!
Look! Princess Sapphire
is cutting the fuses!
But hadn't he ordered
to blow up the city?
But it's... That... it's Sapphire!
It really is Sapphire, damn it!
Nylon, who ordered the
blowing up of the houses?
But... But... But you signed the
official ordinance yourself, didn't you?
- The official ordinance?!
- Well done, Sapphire!
You arrived in time and
you managed to prevent..
. ...the destruction of Silverland!
- You made it too!
Yes, I made it! I want to tell you
one thing, citizens of Silverland!
It was those from Union X
who planted the gunpowder!
Now let's move against them
and let's finish them all off together!
Yes!
Free me, Princess! What
do you intend to do with me?
You will stay where you are until I
have cleared up the doubts about you.
Damn it, they're attacking us!
At them! At them!
Let's kill them all! At them!
Let's get them! At them!
Wait! Wait, you idiots!
Don't run away! Come back!
Fight!
Damn it!
They escaped on the carts!
Curse it! You bunch of cowards!
Damn it!
But look at him! Too bad for him!
The cart is speeding away with him on it!
What happened?
Why wasn't there an explosion?
But what is this earthquake?!
Damn it!
The island! The island is sinking!
Who knows what caused
all this upheaval!
Damn it,
my whole plan has failed!
Poor me!
Princess Sapphire! We are
all extremely grateful to you!
You have saved our city
from destruction!
We cannot celebrate
victory yet!
The Union X army
is approaching us.
But listen:
only if we work together
...all united for the protection
of our homeland,
will we succeed in defeating
our enemies.
It is our only chance of salvation.
Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa
Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo!
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa
Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo!
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
Sen'nen man'nen hyakuman-nen
A thousand years, ten thousand years, a million years,
Ribbon de tsunagou ichioku-nen
Let’s connect with ribbons for a billion years!
Akuma ga kute mo arashi ga kute mo
Even if devils come, even if storms arrive,
tsunaida kokoro wa hanarenai
Our bonded hearts will never part.
Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa
Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo!
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa
Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo!
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
Subtitled by
SilverlandSubs
tinyurl.com/SilverlandSubs
Opening & Ending Song Lyrics Translation by
Natalia Arlovskaya
lyricstranslate.com/en/
translator/natalia-arlovskaya
EAN-13 : 8-031179-423880
ASIN : ‎ B0DQ54LVY1
EAN-13 : 8-031179-426225
ASIN : ‎ B0F1V5YTQP